HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005: A Finding Aid
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005
Baker Library, Harvard Business School
Arch P1
47 boxes, 2 oversize boxes, and 14 mapcase folders
Photographs of faculty and staff of Harvard Business School.
Appointment necessary to consult collection.
Alternative Form Available:
Portions of the collection have been scanned and are available through VIA: http://via.harvard.edu
Historical Note
Harvard Business School was founded in 1908. In the early years many of the faculty members were both traditional academics and "real-world practitioners" recruited from industries to teach at the business school. From the 1920s through the 1950s, many of the new faculty came from HBS MBA and doctoral programs. In addition to teaching and conducting research at HBS, faculty are actively engaged with many outside activities such as serving on boards of directors and as presidents of professional research membership societies, receiving awards, and presenting speeches and lectures. The staff at HBS have been involved in the daily operation of the school as well as conducted research with faculty members.
Scope and Content Note:
The collection consists of photographs of HBS faculty, HBS staff and research fellows. Faculty photographs include many portraits as well as photographs of teaching in classrooms, speaking at various events, social life, researching in faculty offices, and other images documenting the daily activities of HBS faculty.
Staff photographs consist mostly of portraits and also include photographs of staff working in offices and socializing. The collection includes photographs of HBS departments, including the Bureau of Business Research and the Division of Research (later named the Division of Research and Faculty Development), the Audio-Visual department, the Written Analysis of Cases (WAC) graders, and the Office of the Dean and faculty support staff at Morgan Hall, among other departments.
The collection also includes portraits of individuals who have received fellowships at HBS; and portraits of individuals who are affiliated with HBS including donors such as George F. Baker.
Related Collections:
The Faculty and Staff photographs are part of the HBS Archives Photograph Collections. Additional photograph collections include:
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Student Life
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Buildings and Grounds
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Executive Education Programs
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Alumni
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Subject Files and Events
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Wartime Schools
Series Outline
The collection is arranged in the following series:
Series I. Faculty Photographs, 1908-2005
Subseries A. Faculty Photographs, A-Z, 1908-2005
Subseries B. Group Faculty Photographs, 1940s-circa 1990
Subseries C. Unidentified Faculty, circa 1940-circa 2000
Series II. Staff Photographs, 1940-2001
Subseries A. Alphabetical, A-Z, circa 1940-circa 1994
Subseries B. Unidentified Individuals and Contact Sheets, 1940-1989
Subseries C. Departments, A-Z, circa 1922-1980s
Series III. HBS Fellows, A-Z, circa 1954-1994
Series IV. Affiliated Individuals, A-Z, 1920s-circa 1985
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series I. Faculty Photographs, 1908-2005
  This series consists of photographs of faculty members at Harvard Business School. These include full time and visiting faculty from 1908 through the present day, and a few photographs of Harvard University faculty. The photographs document many activities of HBS faculty including teaching, speaking at conferences and other occasions, visiting companies to obtain cases, working in faculty offices, and socializing. Many of the photographs are black and white portraits used for HBS publications. Also included are some photographs of portrait paintings. The Faculty Photographs series has been divided into three subseries, faculty photographs arranged alphabetically; faculty groups arranged chronologically, and unidentified faculty arranged chronologically.
  When it is not evident from the folder title, selected individual folders have a scope and content note to further describe the contents of the folder. Individual faculty members often appear in other faculty members photographs. This has also been noted in folder scope and content notes
  - Subseries A. Faculty Photographs, A-Z, 1908-2005
    - Benjamin Aaron, circa 1972 (Box 1)
    - Charles Cortez Abbott, 1940s (Box 1)
    - Charles Cortez Abbott- Obtaining a case, 1947, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Derek F. Abell, circa 1980 (Box 1)
    - James C. Abegglen, 1983 (Box 1)
    - William J. Abernathy, 1970s-1980s (Box 1)
    - Robert W. Ackerman, 1960s (Box 1)
    - James L. Adams, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Francis J. Aguilar, 1970s (Box 1)
    - Francis J. Aguilar, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Yair Aharoni, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Mark Albion, April 1985 (Box 1)
    - Vernon R. Alden, circa 1950-1960 (Box 1)
    - Vernon R. Alden- Ohio University Presidential Inauguration, 11 May 1962 (Box 1)
    - Peter C. Aldrich, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Brandt Allen, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - Stephen A. Allen, III, circa 1970 (Box 1)
    - Elisabeth K. Allison, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Charles A. Anderson, circa 1948 (Box 1)
    - Leslie Paul Anderson, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Martin L. Anderson, circa 1975 (Box 1)
    - Paul F. Anderson, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Ralph Andreano, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Kenneth R. Andrews, 1948-circa 1960 (Box 1)
    - Kenneth R. Andrews, 1960-1970 (Box 1)
    - Kenneth R. Andrews- Teaching, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Kenneth R. Andrews, 1970s (Box 1)
    - Kenneth R. Andrews, 9 January 1979 (Box 1)
    - Kenneth R. Andrews, 1983-July 1990 (Box 1)
    - Victor Lee Andrews, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Robert Newton Anthony, 1948-1950s (Box 1)
    - Robert Newton Anthony, circa 1950-1960 (Box 1)
    - Robert Newton Anthony, circa 1970-1979 (Box 1)
    - Robert Newton Anthony, 1993 (Box 1)
    - William Applebaum, 1960s (Box 1)
    - Lynda M. Applegate, 1980s (Box 1)
    - Chris Argyris, 1980s (Box 1)
    - Orville F. Armstrong, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Henry B. Arthur, 1960-1965 (Box 1)
    - Henry B. Arthur, 1979-1987 (Box 1)
    - Kenneth Paul Asquith, 1980s (Box 1)
    - Anthony G. Athos, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
    - Anthony G. Athos, 1970s (Box 1)
    - Anthony G. Athos, 1980s (Box 1)
    - Joseph Auerbauch, 1980s (Box 1)
    - Joseph Auerbauch, July 1982 (Box 1)
    - Joseph Auerbauch, 1990s (Box 1)
    - James E. Austin, 1986 (Box 1)
    - James E. Austin, circa 1995 (Box 1)
    - John E. Austin, 1970s (Box 1)
    - Robert W. Austin, 1950s (Box 1)
    - Robert W. Austin, 1960s (Box 1)
    - Henry H. Babcock, 1950s (Box 2)
    - Joseph L. Badaracco, Jr., 1980s (Box 2)
    - Joseph L. Badaracco, Jr., 1989 (Box 2)
    - Joseph C. Bailey, 1948-1950s (Box 2)
    - Joseph C. Bailey, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Joseph C. Bailey, 1970s (Box 2)
    - Joseph C. Bailey- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, 1971 (Box 2)
      Permission to publish must be obtained by the Karsh estate. Contact Archivist for details.
    - John M. Baitsell, 1960s (Box 2)
    - Mart E. Bakal, 1986 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1935-1949 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1950-1954 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1950s (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1960s (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1962 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- On cover of Business Week, 19 January 1963 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- Trip to London, England, 17 April 1964 (Box 2)
      Photographs of Dean Baker in London with Sir John E. Bolton of the HBS Visiting Committee, April 17, 1964
    - George P. Baker, INCAE ceremony in Guatemala, July 1964 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- With Malcolm P. McNair, November-December 1964 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- 25th anniversary of Kress Library at Baker Library, 1964 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1964 (Box 2)
      Includes a group photograph of Dean Baker, John Dearden, James R. Bright, Milton P. Brown, and Charles M. Williams; and photographs of Dean Baker at Bowling Green State University receiving an honorary degree, June 1964.
    - George P. Baker, circa 1965 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- With George Lombard and Myles Mace, circa 1965 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1965 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- Portraits, 1965 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- With Ralph F. Lewis, 16 November 1950 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1966 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, September-October 1966 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, December 1966 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, 1967 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, November 1968 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, December 1968 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, December 1969 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, December 1970s (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker, December 1971 (Box 2)
    - George P. Baker- Portrait painting, circa 1975 (Box 2)
    - Ruth Baker (Wife of George P. Baker), 1970s (Box 2)
    - John Calhoun Baker, 1923-1950s (Box 2)
    - John Calhoun Baker, 1950s-1960s (Box 2)
    - John Calhoun Baker, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Nancy S. Balaguer, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Francis N. Balch, 1932 (Box 2)
    - Louis L. Banks, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Peter J. Barack, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Jack Baranson, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Edward R. Barlow, 1950s (Box 2)
    - Walter D. Barndt, Jr., 1962 (Box 2)
    - Louis B. Barnes, 1970s-1980s (Box 2)
    - Louis B. Barnes, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Louis B. Barnes, 1990s (Box 2)
    - Diana Barrett, circa 1975 (Box 2)
    - M. Edgar Barrett, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Norman J. Bartczak, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Mary E. Barth, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Christopher A. Bartlett, 1984-1987 (Box 3)
    - Christopher A. Bartlett, circa 2000 (Box 3)
    - Fernando Bartolomé- Portraits, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Fernando Bartolomé- Teaching, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Lawrence Barton, 1987 (Box 3)
    - A. John Bates, 1983 (Box 3)
    - A. John Bates, February 1984 (Box 3)
    - George Eugene Bates, 1935-1946 (Box 3)
    - George Eugene Bates, 1946-1949 (Box 3)
    - George Eugene Bates, 1950s (Box 3)
    - George Eugene Bates, 1960-1961 (Box 3)
    - George Eugene Bates, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Gilbert L. Bates, 1948 (Box 3)
    - Raymond A. Bauer, 1970s (Box 3)
    - James P. Baughman, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Norton M. Bedford, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Michael Beer, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Michael Beer, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Michael Beer, 1984-July 1993 (Box 3)
    - Michael Beer, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Robert D. Behn, 1973 (Box 3)
    - David E. Bell, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Gerald D. Bell, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Earl D. Bennett, 1956 (Box 3)
    - John S. Bennett, 1970s (Box 3)
    - Lawrence A. Bennigson, 1970s (Box 3)
    - Norman A. Berg, 1965-1980s (Box 3)
    - Adolf Augustus Berle, 1928 (Box 3)
    - Kenneth Bernhardt, February 1984 (Box 3)
    - Marc L. Bertoneche, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Santosh Kumar Bhattacharyya, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Amarnath Bhide, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Amarnath Bhide, circa 1993 (Box 3)
    - Clinton Post Biddle, 1923 (Box 3)
    - Clinton Post Biddle, circa 1925, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Clinton Post Biddle- Portrait painting, circa 1925, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Richmond Fletcher Bingham, 1927 (Box 3)
    - David Birch, circa 1970 (Box 3)
    - Harvey P. Bishop, circa 1948 (Box 3)
    - Harvey P. Bishop, 1950s (Box 3)
    - Harvey P. Bishop- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - John E. Bishop- Portraits, 1960s (Box 3)
    - John E. Bishop- Looking at computers with F. Warren McFarlan, circa 1975 (Box 3)
    - John E. Bishop- Teaching, 1970s (Box 3)
    - Calvin P. Blair, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Arthur L. Blakeslee, 1979 (Box 3)
    - Colin C. Blaydon, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Charles Andressen Bliss, 1938-1949 (Box 3)
    - Charles Andressen Bliss, 1950s (Box 3)
    - Charles Andressen Bliss, 1960s (Box 3)
    - Charles Andressen Bliss, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Charles Andressen Bliss, 19 September 1977 (Box 3)
    - David Bloomfield, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Lee Bodenhamer, 1968 (Box 3)
    - Zvi Bodie, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Derek Bok- Speaking at Diebold Lecture, 9 March 1970 (Box 3)
    - Derek Bok, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Mike Boland, 1985-1987 (Box 3)
    - Lynn Louis Bollinger, circa 1939-1950s (Box 3)
    - Kurt Borchardt, 1970s (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1932-1948 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden- On cover of Tide magazine, 22 March 1946 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1950s (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1954 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden- Portrait, 1954 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, circa 1955 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize box) (Mapcase)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1958-1960 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1960s (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden- Portraits, 1960s (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Neil H. Borden, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Gordon Townley Bowden, 1941 (Box 4)
    - H. Kent Bowen, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Joseph L. Bower- With Sam Hayes, 1982 (Box 4)
    - Joseph L. Bower, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Joseph L. Bower, circa 2000 (Box 4)
    - George E. P. Box, 1966 (Box 4)
    - James E. Boyce, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Keith Bradey, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Stephen P. Bradley, 1970 (Box 4)
    - Stephen P. Bradley, circa 1995 (Box 4)
    - Thornton F. Bradshaw, 1947-1983 (Box 4)
    - Adam Brandenburger, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Floyd S. Brandt, 1959 (Box 4)
    - James R. Bright, 1956-1960s (Box 4)
    - James R. Bright, circa 1960 (Box 4)
    - Andrew F. Brimmer, 1974 (Box 4)
    - Andrew F. Brimmer, circa 1975 (Box 4)
    - Dwight S. Brothers, 1960s (Box 4)
    - Dwight S. Brothers, circa 1970 (Box 4)
    - Donald A. Brown, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Milton P. Brown, 1946 (Box 4)
    - Milton P. Brown- With Malcolm P. McNair and Elizabeth A. Burnham, 1949 (Box 4)
    - Milton P. Brown, 1964-1989 (Box 4)
    - Rex V. Brown, 1965 (Box 4)
    - Ronald Gene Brown, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Theodore H. Brown, 1937 (Box 4)
    - Theodore H. Brown, 1938 (Box 4)
    - Theodore H. Brown, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
    - Theodore H. Brown- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 4)
    - William J. Bruns, 1970 (Box 4)
    - William J. Bruns, 1989 (Box 4)
    - William J. Bruns, 1992 (Box 4)
    - William J. Bruns, circa 2000 (Box 4)
    - Jack R. Buchanan, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Stanley I. Buchin, 1965 (Box 4)
    - Elwood S. Buffa, 1964 (Box 4)
    - Douglas R. Bunker, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Irving C. Bupp, 1970s (Box 4)
    - Elizabeth Abbott Burnham, 1948 (Box 4)
    - Elizabeth Abbott Burnham, 1950s (Box 4)
    - Cecil Lloyd Burrill, 1938 (Box 4)
    - Edward C. Bursk, 1946-1949 (Box 4)
    - Edward C. Bursk- With Howard Lewis and James Cullinton, 1949 (Box 4)
    - Edward C. Bursk, 1960s (Box 4)
    - J. Keith Butters, circa 1948-1970s (Box 4)
    - J. Keith Butters, 1980s (Box 4)
    - J. Keith Butters, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Dale E. Butz, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Robert D. Buzzell, circa 1963-1984 (Box 4)
    - Hugh Cabot, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Philip Cabot, 1928 (Box 5)
    - Philip Cabot, 1937 (Box 5)
    - Philip Cabot, 1938 (Box 5)
    - Philip Cabot, 1940s (Box 5)
    - Philip Cabot, 1941 (Box 5)
    - John F. Cady, 1977 (Box 5)
    - John G. Callan, 1938 (Box 5)
    - John G. Callan- Portrait painting, 1938 (Box 5)
    - Robert H. Caplan, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Richard N. Cardozzo, 1965- circa 1975 (Box 5)
    - Robert S. Carlson, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Vincent P. Carosso, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Thomas Henry Carroll, 1937-1960 (Box 5)
    - Ernest Eugene Carter, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Everett N. Case, 1939 (Box 5)
    - Everett N. Case- With Wallace Brett Donham, circa 1940 (Box 5)
    - Cornelius J. Casey, Jr., 1978 (Box 5)
    - James I. Cash, Jr.- With Robert G. Eccles, 1980s (Box 5)
    - James I. Cash, Jr., 1990s (Box 5)
    - Frank V. Cespedes, circa 1993 (Box 5)
    - Robert Willis Chambers, 1939 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, circa 1980 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, circa 1981 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, circa 1982 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler, circa 1985 (Box 5)
    - Alfred D. Chandler- Teaching, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Eliot Dismore Chapple, 1937 (Box 5)
    - Richard B. Chase, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Paul W. Cherington, 1953 (Box 5)
    - Paul W. Cherington, circa 1960 (Box 5)
    - Paul W. Cherington, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Paul W. Cherington, 1970 (Box 5)
    - W. Bruce Chew, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Dong Sung Cho, 1984 (Box 5)
    - C. Roland Christensen, 1948 (Box 6)
    - C. Roland Christensen, 1960 (Box 6)
    - C. Roland Christensen, 1965 (Box 6)
    - C. Roland Christensen, 1990 (Box 6)
    - C. Roland Christensen- Retirement party, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Clayton Christensen, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Charles J. Christenson, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Charles J. Christenson, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Charles J. Christenson, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Charles J. Christenson, 1980s (Box 6)
    - Charles J. Christenson, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Evelyn T. Christiansen, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Neil C. Churchill, 1967-1970s (Box 6)
    - Ralph DeArmond Cies, 1939 (Box 6)
    - Ralph Shaw Claire, 1941 (Box 6)
    - James V. Clark, 1956-1961 (Box 6)
    - Kim Clark, 1980s (Box 6)
    - Kim Clark- With William J. Abernathy and Alan Kantrow, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Kim Clark, 1990s (Box 6)
    - Kim Clark, circa 1998 (Box 6)
    - Kim Clark, circa 1998-2001 (Box 6)
    - Kim Clark- Portraits, circa 2001 (Box 6)
    - Kim Clark- Farewell party, August 2005 (Box 6)
    - Darral G. Clarke, 1973 (Box 7)
    - James G. Clawson, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Paul B. Coffman, 1935 (Box 7)
    - Daniel J. Cohrs, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Arthur H. Cole, 1930s (Box 7)
    - Arthur H. Cole, 1940s (Box 7)
    - Arthur H. Cole, circa 1950 (Box 7)
    - Arthur H. Cole- With Donald T. Clark, circa 1950 (Box 7)
    - Arthur H. Cole- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, 1956 (Box 7)
    - Arthur H. Cole- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, 1956, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Arthur H. Cole- Christmas party, December 1959 (Box 7)
    - David L. Cole, 1974 (Box 7)
    - William Morse Cole, 1932 (Box 7)
    - William Morse Cole- Portrait painting, circa 1935, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Alan B. Coleman, 1961 (Box 7)
    - John Coleman, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Morgan Collins, 1966 (Box 7)
    - James Bryant Conant, circa 1933 (Box 7)
    - James Bryant Conant, 1943-1946 (Box 7)
    - James Bryant Conant, 1947-1953 (Box 7)
    - James Bryant Conant, circa 1950 (Box 7)
    - James Bryant Conant, circa 1950, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Jay A. Conger, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Alfred H. Conrad, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Paul W. Cook, Jr., 1956 (Box 7)
    - John Cleveland Cooley, 1941 (Box 7)
    - Arnold C. Cooper, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Robin Cooper, 1979 (Box 7)
    - William W. Cooper, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Paul H. Cootner, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland- Notes regarding photographs (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland- Comptrollers Conference, 1921 (Box 7)
      Melvin T. Copeland, Donald K. David and other researchers displaying a chart at the Comptrollers Conference, 1921.
    - Melvin T. Copeland- Automotive Equipment Association, 31 July 1925 (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland, 1932-1935 (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland, 1950s (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland- Portrait painting, circa 1950 (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland- Speaking at Algonquin Club, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland- At desk, circa 1955 (Box 7)
    - Melvin T. Copeland, 1973 (Box 7)
    - E. Raymond Corey, 1960 (Box 7)
    - E. Raymond Corey- In classroom, 1960s (Box 7)
    - E. Raymond Corey- With Miles Mace, 1960s (Box 7)
    - E. Raymond Corey, 1970s (Box 7)
    - E. Raymond Corey, 1978-1984 (Box 7)
    - E. Raymond Corey, 1989 (Box 7)
    - E. Raymond Corey, 1990s (Box 7)
    - C. Christopher Cox, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Clifton B. Cox, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Donald F. Cox, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Gail Gramer, circa 1965 (Box 7)
    - Dwight B. Crane, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Dwight B. Crane, 1990s (Box 7)
    - Edward Kneeland Cratsley, 1938-1939 (Box 7)
    - Neil L. Crone, circa 1948 (Box 7)
    - M. Colyer Crum, 1970 (Box 7)
    - M. Colyer Crum, 1980s (Box 7)
    - Robert D. Cuff, 1985 (Box 7)
    - James W. Culliton, 1948 (Box 7)
    - James W. Culliton, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Scott M. Cunningham, 1965 (Box 7)
    - William J. Cunningham, 1933-1935 (Box 7)
    - William J. Cunningham, 1945 (Box 7)
    - Herman P.C. Daems, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Gene W. Dalton, 1963 (Box 7)
    - John E. Dalton, 1935 (Box 7)
    - Srikant M. Datar, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Donald Hills Davenport, 1931 (Box 7)
    - Thomas H. Davenport, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Donald K. David- Clippings and ephemera related to photographs (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1940s (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- American Maize Products Co. events, 1940-1946 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Motto outside conference room, 1942 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- With Office of the Dean staff, circa 1943 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Portrait painting, 1943 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Portrait painting, circa 1943, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Donald K. David, 1943 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Wartime Schools, 1943-1946 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Wartime Schools event, 1943 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1944 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1946 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1947 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Receiving honorary degree from St. Lawrence University, 1947 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1948 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, circa 1949 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1949 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Portraits, circa 1950 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1950s (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- With Ford Motor Co. Directors, circa 1950, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Donald K. David, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- With Malcolm P. McNair and Lincoln Filene, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Portrait painting, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Looking at model on new buildings on campus, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Portraits, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, ca. 1952, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Donald K. David, 1952 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- With Office of the Dean staff, 1952 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Receiving honorary degree from Carlton College, 30 June 1952 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1953 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1952- With Nathan Pusey and Ralph Lowell at Visiting Committee meeting, December 1953 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1952- Public Relations Society of America, 31 December 1953 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1954 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Donald K. David, circa 1955, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Donald K. David, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Farewell party, 1955 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Portrait painting, [1955] (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David- Norwegian Consul event, 18 March 1955 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Donald K. David, 1976-1978 (Box 8)
    - Philip Davidowitz, 1967 (Box 9)
    - William R. Davidson, circa 1965 (Box 9)
    - Edward W. Davis, 1968 (Box 9)
    - John H. Davis, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Robert Tyrrell Davis, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Stanley M. Davis, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Warren Davis, circa 1965 (Box 9)
    - DeWitt C. Dearborn, 1953 (Box 9)
    - John Dearden, 1961 (Box 9)
    - F. Stewart De Bruicker, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
    - J. Anton de Haas, 1933-1935 (Box 9)
    - J. Anton de Haas, 1947 (Box 9)
    - Thomas J. DeLong, 1987 (Box 9)
    - J. Harold DeNike, 1938 (Box 9)
    - E. Hazel Denton, 1976 (Box 9)
    - A. S. Dewing, circa 1930 (Box 9)
    - Bala G. Dharan, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Anirudh Dhebar, circa 1989 (Box 9)
    - Allen Briggs Dickerman, 1943 (Box 9)
    - David Bruce Dill, 1936 (Box 9)
    - Samuel I. Doctors, circa 1980 (Box 9)
    - Robert J. Dolan, 1981-1989 (Box 9)